Kimberly Champagne

T: (954) 914-4874 E: contact@kimberlychampagne.com

Objective

To succeed in applying the knowledge and experience gained through studying psychology statistics, and software coding to tackle any task handed to me. To also grow in a stimulating environment that will provide me with opportunities to learn, and make great connections while contributing as much as possible to meet the company's goals.

Education

The Honors College at Florida State University, Tallahassee, Florida

May 2017

- o Full-time undergraduate student studying Psychology and Statistics.
- Conducted an Honors Thesis, which required statistical analysis on large datasets and wrote a final report that was chosen for publication
 - Thesis: Predictors of Mobile Device Usage and Proficiency among Older Adults
- Chosen to present my Honors Thesis at the Human-Computer Interaction Conference in Vancouver, Canada
 - Will be published in their yearly volume set (published by Springer)
- o Research assistant in numerous labs.
 - Assisted in the Florida Department of Transportation lab at FSU under Dr. Walter Boot and Dr. Neil Charness
 - Worked on numerous research studies using a Driving Simulator and analyzed data.
 - Volunteered in the KATLAB studying the neural markers of anxiety in children under Dr. Alexandra Meyer.
- Presented data from the Florida Department of Transportation (FDOT) lab at Undergraduate Research Day and Psychology Undergraduate Research Day, held yearly and attended by our school president, other administration and professors
- Completed my Statistics minor by pursuing a SAS certificate, which requires 4 courses with the coding program implemented.
- Proficient in **R**, which was heavily taught in my statistics courses (primarily biostatistics)
- o Proficient in **SPSS**, which was also implemented in many of my courses.
- Proficient in HTML and CSS (learned through Code Academy online) I have experience using those two languages to design websites.
- Learning **Python** through the book Think Python: An Introduction to Software Design by Allen B. Downey
- o Learned **Javascript** through Code Academy online.
- Political Science Learning coordinator for the Catalyst Club under the Black Student Union at Florida State.
- o Graduating as an Honors student through FSU's Honors in the Major Program
- o GPA: 3.98
- The Honors College at Florida International University, Miami, Florida 2015

May

- Full-time sophomore student studying Pre-Med and Psychology in their Honors College program.
- Broward College, Pembroke Pines, Florida

May 2014

- o Enrolled in their Early Admissions program for high school students.
- $\circ \quad$ AP Scholar graduating high school with over a year of college completed
- Took 4 AP classes (AP Art History, AP language Arts, AP American History, and AP World History)
- o Graduated top 15% of my class with a 4.5 GPA

Experience

Evans Economic Consulting Agency

- May 2017 currently
- Helped clean and organize large data sets for statistical analysis by this company.
- AppleCare At-Home Advisor / Apple Internship

January 2016 – currently

- Technical advisor for all IOS (iPhones, iPads, and iPods) devices, as well as their compatibility with customer's computers
- Team MVP numerous times because of outstanding metrics
- Learned about the rich business history of this company, as well as the software and hardware that has been manufactured by them over the years
- o Consistently lead the team in issue resolution time and customer satisfaction
- $\circ\quad$ Consistently met or exceeded expectations during every quarterly performance review
- Given accolades by management in the Student Union employee recognition page emailed to everyone that's a part of the college program
- o Chosen as an extender in the college program after the 1 year internship was over
- o Chosen to extend to a permanent position at Apple, after graduation in May 2017
- Fontainebleau Pool Greeter Miami Beach, Florida

May 2015

- Pool greeter, checking room keys at the entrance and stocking cabanas.
- o Participated in the Joe Dimaggio Children's Hospital yearly Gala with Marc Anthony, Don Francisco, and Frankie J in attendance.
- Outback Steakhouse, Davie, Florida

October 2014-March 2015

- Server with full-bar training
- o Ensured customer satisfaction in a timely manner
- o Made sure service and meal preparation was superb.
- · Chick-Fil-A Fountains of Miramar, Miramar, Florida

December 2011-August 2013

- Certified trainer responsible for ensuring new hire's understanding of their position and responsibilities in the restaurant.
- Responsible for ensuring my own front of house duties while having to make sure customer service met Chick-Fil-A's outstanding standards.
- o Great preparation for my up coming jobs in the fine dining industry.

Community Service

- Children's Harbor Foster Home Volunteer through PPCHS T.R.O.O.P Club August 2010-May 2012
 - Through my High School's T.R.O.O.P club (Teens Reaching Out to Other People), of which I was treasurer, every month we would visit the Children's Harbor foster home in our community
 - Over a span of 2 years, we would visit the foster children here, bringing them toys and clothes.
 - We would fundraise for goods at our school, so that more people could be involved to bring about a change.
 - We would talk to the children who ranged in age from toddler to seventeen, and the connection and understanding our group experienced was priceless.
- PPCHS Job Fair Creator and Volunteer

August 2010-May 2012

- \circ $\;$ Through my high school's T.R.O.O.P club, we created our school's first job fair, recruiting job sponsors and setting up the venue.
- Abundant Living Ministries Nursery Worker, Pembroke Pines, Florida September 2009-May 2014

- At 15, I became a nursery volunteer at the church I grew up in, Abundant Living Ministries.
- o Took charge of the 3-4 year old department, creating weekly Sunday school courses while watching over, feeding, and ensuring the safety of every child there.

٠

- Dixie Shelton, Apple Manager
 - 0 (501) 940-4641

References

- Dr. Walter Boot, Florida Department of Transportation Research Lab Director and personal Honors Thesis director
 - 0 850 644 2040
 - o boot@psy.fsu.edu